[
  {
    "question": "According to the lectures, why is it important to have an in depth understanding of the history of ESL/EFL?",
    "answers": [
      "to have a deeper insight into your own teaching theory and practices"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lectures, what are the elements you are invited to examine in each teaching approach?",
    "answers": ["purpose, content, technique"]
  },
  {
    "question": "“Why should we teach languages?” is asked in order to establish",
    "answers": ["purpose"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lectures, why is the content of each teaching approach important to examine?",
    "answers": ["to consider the materials used for teaching each approach."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is not a question that would allow for a discussion of teacher technique?",
    "answers": ["Who should we teach?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why was the idea that “purpose shapes both content and technique” emphasized?",
    "answers": [
      "because content and technique are changed and adapted for each purpose."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which answer is NOT a primary reason for the the use of caricatures in the upcoming videos?",
    "answers": ["to entertain the viewers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Peter Elbow is associated with the idea of",
    "answers": ["the believing and doubting game"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The artistic examples of abstract expressionism and the photorealism movement were used to show",
    "answers": [
      "how the pendulum swings back and forth, creating extreme opposites of the former movement."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the pendular swing most prominent in the field of language teaching?",
    "answers": ["1880-1980"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is an example of a chain drill?",
    "answers": [
      "Student 1:  I like tennis.\n\nStudent 2:  She likes tennis.  I like football.\n\nStudent 3:  She likes tennis.  He likes football.  I like baseball."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach utilizes chain drills, as demonstrated above?",
    "answers": ["The Audio-lingual Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach became popular as a result of standardized tests, such as the Scholastic Aptitude Test, or the SAT?",
    "answers": ["The Reading Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approaches focused mainly on language production, specifically listening and speaking skills?",
    "answers": ["The Direct Approach", "The Audio Lingual Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "As a result of pedagogical developments, teachers now continue to utilize vocabulary list memorization, but to a lesser extent than that of the Reading Approach in the 1930's.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach combined memorization and automatic responses?",
    "answers": ["The Audio-lingual Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the main purpose of using minimal pairs in the Audio Lingual Approach?",
    "answers": ["To improve pronunciation."]
  },
  {
    "question": "The use of textbooks in the classroom was vital for the success of students acquiring language using the Audio Lingual Approach.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which activity uses scaffolding to help students better understand and comprehend readings?",
    "answers": ["Guided Reading"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approaches are more suited to students who probably won't need to use or speak the target language outside the classroom?",
    "answers": ["The Grammar Translation Approach", "The Reading Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following can be considered components of the multiple concert technique? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Listening to a dramatic reading while following along with a script.",
      "Completing an outline of notes.",
      "Taking notes of a dialogue."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is not actually a classroom approach?",
    "answers": ["The Cognitive Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Affective Humanistic approach focused on students’ feelings.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lectures, why is positive reinforcement an effective classroom technique?",
    "answers": [
      "It encourages learners to take risks and feel comfortable making mistakes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach would most likely be taught by someone interested in expanding the mind and helping people calm their anxieties?",
    "answers": ["The Affective Humanistic Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach was strongly influenced by behaviorism?",
    "answers": ["The Audio Lingual Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which are characteristics of the Cognitive Approach? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Student errors became of particular interest to researchers.",
      "It never truly developed into a classroom methodology."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which activities might have helped students of an Affective Humanistic teacher to learn language more quickly?",
    "answers": ["Singing", "Dancing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach is Noam Chomsky most closely associated with?",
    "answers": ["The Cognitive Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What were the main focuses of the Affective Humanistic Approach? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Making learners comfortable",
      "Providing a soothing environment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which linguistic theorists are most closely associated with the Comprehension Approach?",
    "answers": ["Stephen Krashen", "James J. Asher"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach utilizes the technique of using commands combined with observable physical actions for students to observe and follow?",
    "answers": ["Comprehension Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which aspects of the Comprehension Approach are similar to the Direct Approach?",
    "answers": [
      "Focus on making meaning clear.",
      "Learners have time to process language before producing the language."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A Korean langauge teacher brings in a map for the Seoul subway system and asks students to create conversations in Korean about transportation using the information provided in the map. This is an example of",
    "answers": ["Use of authentic materials"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main purpose of TPR (Total Physical Response) activities?",
    "answers": ["to make meaning clear to students"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach encourages learners to develop an appreciation for the target people, culture and place by connecting with them through language and use of meaningful communication?",
    "answers": ["Communicative Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these are teaching methods used in the Communicative Approach? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Use of level-appropriate books with high interest themes.",
      "Use of books focusing on all four language skills:  reading, writing, listening and speaking",
      "Use of food, music, posters and costumes"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach would most likely advocate for \"English Only\" classrooms?",
    "answers": ["Comprehension Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these are a focus of the Communicative Approach? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "to connect people together in order to create opportunity and awareness.",
      "to love other cultures and places.",
      "to use the target language."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When students assume the role of the teacher by giving commands to other students and the teacher, this is called",
    "answers": ["Role reversal"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approaches focused on the oral production of language? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "The Direct Approach",
      "The Audio-lingual Approach",
      "The Affective Humanistic Approach",
      "The Communicative Approach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language approaches swung to the other side of the pendulum, placing more emphasis on non-speaking language skills, such as grammar, reading and writing? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": ["The Grammar Translation Approach", "The Reading Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach did not offer actual techniques for classroom instruction, instead it used research to better comprehend learners minds and the workings of language?",
    "answers": ["The Cognitive Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for the technique of using commands combined with observable physical actions for students to observe and follow?",
    "answers": ["TPR (Total Physical Response)"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language approach utilized the following techniques: habit formation drills, minimal pairs, dialogues, and memorization?",
    "answers": ["The Audio-lingual Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which techniques are most commonly associated as part of the Communicative Approach? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Sequencing Activities",
      "Information Gap Activities",
      "Use of Authentic Materials",
      "Role Plays"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the videos, what are the three elements that teachers can think about when reviewing different teaching philosophies?",
    "answers": ["Purpose", "Content", "Technique"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the lectures, which of the following questions are related to purpose? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": ["Why should we teach language?", "Who should we teach?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the purpose of \"back translation?\"",
    "answers": [
      "to help learners precisely understand language forms and vocabulary."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the Communicative Approach come about? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "People were traveling more, for both work and pleasure, which heightened the need to communicate in foreign language.",
      "People didn't have time to sit and process language until they were  ready to speak it. They needed a faster way to study language.",
      "People began to realize that more than just grammar and vocabulary  knowledge were necessary to effectively communicate in another language."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approaches promote learning culture as an important part of language acquisition? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": ["The Direct Approach", "The Communicative Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following approaches believe that memorizing grammar and vocabulary are imperative to learning language? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": ["The Grammar Translation Approach", "The Reading Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are aspects of the \"silent period\" concept? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "learners might not be confident enough to speak the target language, so they remain silent.",
      "learners don't know enough of the language to begin speaking, so they remain silent."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it important to have an in-depth understanding of the history of ESL/EFL?",
    "answers": [
      "to have a deeper insight into your own teaching theory and practices."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Comprehension Approach uses which of the following techniques? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "TPR (Total Physical Response)",
      "Encouraging the utilization of the \"silent period\"",
      "Role Reversal"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Direct Approach should utilize two languages: The learner’s first language and the target language the learner is studying.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which linguist was the inspiration for the use of the \"Angel\" and \"Devil\" videos in this course?",
    "answers": ["Peter Elbow"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who put forth the idea that students learn language through comprehensible input and that teaching should focus on helping students comprehend a language, similar to how a child learns his/her first language?",
    "answers": ["Stephen Krashen"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Direct Approach asserts that people learn a second language just as children learn their first language by exploring the world around them. Select all the arguments that support this claim.",
    "answers": [
      "Learners, like children, develop skills through predictable sequences.",
      "Using visual aids and objects in the language classroom enables learners, and children, to acquire language more effectively."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach asserts that the use of motivational devices, such as games, help students with language acquisition?",
    "answers": ["The Communicative Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is an example of a \"chain drill?\"",
    "answers": [
      "Student 1:  I like tennis.\n\nStudent 2:  She likes tennis.  I like football.\n\nStudent 3:  She likes tennis.  He likes football.  I like baseball."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach features \"chain drills?\"",
    "answers": ["The Audio-lingual Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are components of the multiple concert technique from the Affective Humanistic Approach? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Listening to a dramatic reading while following along with a script.",
      "Completing an outline of notes.",
      "Taking notes of a dialogue."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language approach do most teachers align themselves with today?",
    "answers": ["The Communicative Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which activity from the Reading Approach uses scaffolding to help students better understand and comprehend readings?",
    "answers": ["Guided Reading"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which year did the lectures associate with the Direct Approach?",
    "answers": ["1910"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which books/materials might have been used by language teachers during the Grammar Translation Method? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "The Writings of Aristotle",
      "The Writings of Cicero",
      "The New Testament",
      "The Writings of Homer (Odyssey, Illiad)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which was NOT an acceptable method of helping students remember the target language using the Grammar Translation Approach?",
    "answers": ["Acting out the texts that are being studied"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A word in a target language that is similar to the native language is called a(n)",
    "answers": ["cognate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Direct Approach was specifically designed for wealthy, young men.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why did the teacher from the Direct Approach describe his time with the Oohooto tribe?",
    "answers": [
      "To show how he totally immersed himself in the Oohooto language and culture."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the Direct Approach, listening and speaking skills are de-emphasized.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which approach focuses on expressly using the target language in classes.",
    "answers": ["The Direct Approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The Direct Approach asserts that people learn a second language just as children learn their first language by exploring the world around them. Check the arguments that support this claim.",
    "answers": [
      "Learners, like children, develop skills through predictable sequences.",
      "Using visual aids and objects in the language classroom enables learners, and children, to acquire language more effectively."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which techniques could be used in a Direct Approach classroom? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Use of Maps",
      "Enactment of plays and skits",
      "Encouragement of Student Self-Correction",
      "Use of Drawing Pictures based on Dictation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jerome Bruner, a cognitive learning theorist, suggests that curriculum should be built:",
    "answers": ["in a spiral, from simple to complex."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are effective strategies to help students connect prior knowledge to new material? (Choose two)",
    "answers": [
      "Ask students what they know about a topic in an objective discussion.",
      "Include visuals, questions prompts or short videos in a warm up."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following ESL Activities is most likely to help students connect to previous knowledge?",
    "answers": ["Think, pair, square, share activities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What three things should a warm up lesson include?",
    "answers": [
      "introduction of new ideas",
      "a description of how learning will be measured",
      "an \"attention getter\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Knowing your objectives is important because: (select three answers)",
    "answers": [
      "You will be able to clarify how and what you will instruct.",
      "You will be better able to prioritize the content of your lesson.",
      "Students are more likely to succeed when they know their target goals."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two features should a lesson objective include?",
    "answers": [
      "A way to measure or assess learning",
      "Action words like \"identify, complete, match, or write\""
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Blumenfeld and Krajcik's theory says that objectives should result in a meaningful project. An example of this might be: (Select two answers)",
    "answers": ["a student portfolio", "A final class presentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best example of a strong lesson objective?",
    "answers": [
      "Students will be able to use the simple past tense to write a paragraph describing an event in their childhood."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following ESL Activities are good examples of measuring student understanding? (Select three answers)",
    "answers": [
      "A journal reflecting on the day's activities",
      "A Cloze exercise using the day's vocabulary words",
      "A jigsaw where students present different pieces of an article or story"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of objectives or content that matters?",
    "answers": [
      "Including relevant examples of the 2000 most-used words in English in your course lesson.",
      "Including the most frequently-used verb tenses (simple present, simple past, present perfect) in English in your lesson.",
      "Including necessary vocabulary to teach a specific unit theme that your lesson is based on."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the name of the man whose theories of instructional design these videos focused on?",
    "answers": ["Robert Gagne"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is meant by “present by staying in the present?”",
    "answers": [
      "When you present content, be sure to do so in a lively, engaging manner that draws students in and motivates them to learn more."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The providing “learner guidance” stage of instruction encourages students to do which 4 activities?",
    "answers": [
      "Play with language",
      "Make mistakes",
      "Figure out how certain rules or words work",
      "Interact with each other in order to acquire language"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Benjamin Bloom, a learning theorist, suggested which 2 ideas?",
    "answers": [
      "A good instructor is able to use many different methods to get students to interact with learning.",
      "A good instructor is able to motivate students to think and examine information critically."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three (3) activities are examples of eliciting performance?",
    "answers": ["A test", "A presentation", "A group activity"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three (3) activities that can be used for presenting content?",
    "answers": [
      "Demonstrating and sharing",
      "Giving explicit information that will help learners understand material",
      "Speaking and presenting"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This course will introduce you to which of the following principles?",
    "answers": ["Lesson Design and Assessment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Students do not need to share what they know and be engaged in the learning process.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the first video, Ms. Cinco mentioned that “Super smart people learn from _________ experiences” in the introduction video in hopes that participants in this course can learn both the good and bad in the course. (Choose the missing words.)",
    "answers": ["other people’s"]
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the most significant roles of a teacher is as a lesson planner, which generally happens when students aren’t around.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of how to make instruction \"sticky?\" (Choose three)",
    "answers": [
      "Use of acronyms",
      "Keeping things conversational",
      "Modeling information"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best description of \"sticky\" instruction?",
    "answers": ["Memorable, usable, durable"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good strategies for keeping classes conversational? (select two)",
    "answers": [
      "Elicit reactions and responses from your students.",
      "Share appropriate personal information."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good examples of \"teacher talk?\" (Select three):",
    "answers": [
      "Using board work to introduce your topic",
      "Using metaphors and analogies",
      "Clarify and elaborate when students don't understand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are good examples of teacher modeling? (Select two)",
    "answers": [
      "Show several student examples to illustrate the assignment.",
      "Sharing your own work so that students can see what you have done."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of teaching using inductive reasoning? (select two)",
    "answers": [
      "Give students a problem to solve in pairs or groups.",
      "Ask students to find common themes in a group of illustrations."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A teacher shows students three poems, then asks them to write their own poem. This is an example of:",
    "answers": ["modeling"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A teacher shows two videos and asks students what themes they have in common. This is an example of:",
    "answers": ["inductive reasoning"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following represents the concept of teaching using inductive reasoning?",
    "answers": ["Model, infer, and elaborate"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is usually best to show students a model first, before introducing a lesson using inductive reasoning.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the correct sequence for instruction, modeling and practice?",
    "answers": [
      "Present instruction, model, guided practice, independent practice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it important to give students guided practice opportunities? (Choose 3 answers)",
    "answers": [
      "It allows students hands-on practice with the information learned in class before they are asked to do things on their own.",
      "It gives students time to comprehend and process what they have learned.",
      "It provides students a safety net, so they are not afraid of making mistakes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one method for keeping students engaged during guided practice activities?",
    "answers": [
      "Starting a sentence and letting students finish it by filling in the correct information."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The teacher should be in front of the classroom with all students watching him/her during less-guided practice activities.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two ways to improve group-directed activities?",
    "answers": [
      "Give low-performing students the most difficult tasks.",
      "Ensure that groups are of mixed levels and abilities."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the purpose of independent practice activities? (Check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "give the teacher an opportunity to see what students have really learned",
      "gives the students an opportunity to show that they have understood the lesson"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two examples of independent practice activities are:",
    "answers": [
      "Students give a presentation relating new information to the class.",
      "Students write an essay."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When facilitating independent practices, a teacher should:",
    "answers": ["Walk around the room, checking work and answering questions."]
  },
  {
    "question": "If a large number of students have trouble with an independent practice assignment, it is best to:",
    "answers": ["supply additional guided practice for the class."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Teacher should always give students a grade for their independent practice activities.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following educational practices is best assessed by a performance-based assessment tool?",
    "answers": ["Communicative approach"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three of the following words are appropriate to a test of higher-order thinking?",
    "answers": ["evaluate", "create", "analyze"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three of the following are examples of authentic assessment?",
    "answers": [
      "A student portfolio",
      "A letter to the local paper",
      "A science project"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three of the following are examples of summative assessments?",
    "answers": [
      "A final exam",
      "A multiple-choice quiz",
      "A five-paragraph essay"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three of the following are examples of formative assessments?",
    "answers": ["A student portfolio", "A class discussion", "An ungraded quiz"]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is important to grade everything that students do in class so that you will have the best idea of their performance.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three advantages of using a rubric to evaluate student work?",
    "answers": [
      "Students have a clear picture of how their work will be assessed.",
      "Students can use the rubric to assess their own or their peers' work.",
      "Teachers can grade more consistently and evaluate student progress more quickly."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are two examples of peer review?",
    "answers": [
      "Students use a rubric to give feedback on their classmate's presentation.",
      "Students work together to develop a quiz or assignment for the class."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three of the following are effective \"shortcuts\" to save a teacher's time when providing feeback?",
    "answers": [
      "Create a list of \"error codes.\"",
      "Use technology to create surveys to check student understanding.",
      "Create relevant, clear rubrics."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The main purpose of most language courses today is:",
    "answers": ["to facilitate communication in the target language"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the topic of this course?",
    "answers": ["Lesson Design and Assessment"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which event was not included in Robert Gagne's theory of instructional design?",
    "answers": ["The need for explicit lesson plans"]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Warm language\" is language that",
    "answers": ["draws students in and motivates them."]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Eliciting performance\" is NOT achieved by",
    "answers": ["lecturing students."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following activities is most likely to help students connect to previous knowledge?",
    "answers": ["Think, pair, square, share activities."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which activity should NOT be included in a warm up lesson?",
    "answers": ["Long-term goals for the class"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The providing \"learner guidance\" stage of instruction encourages students to do which four activities?",
    "answers": [
      "Play with language",
      "Make mistakes",
      "Figure out how certain rules or words work",
      "Interact with each other in order to acquire language."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Benjamin Bloom a learning theorist, suggested which two ideas?",
    "answers": [
      "Many different ways can be used to get students to interact with learning.",
      "A good instructor is able to motivate students to think and examine information critically."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Three important reasons to stimulate background knowledge (recall) are:",
    "answers": [
      "Students are more likely to engage in the learning process if they share what they already know.",
      "It can help you in the selection of student helpers for the classroom.",
      "Students will be more receptive to learning new material"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Present by staying in the present\" means:",
    "answers": ["Present your content in a lively, engaging manner."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three strategies will help to engage learners from the start?",
    "answers": [
      "Fire up their neural receptors",
      "Connect lesson plans to each other.",
      "Connect new information to prior knowledge."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two things a lesson plan objective should include are:",
    "answers": [
      "Action words such as: identify, state, or demonstrate",
      "A clear statement of measurable outcomes."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A lesson plan objective should NOT include: (Choose all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "long term goals",
      "action words like: comprehend, feel, learn",
      "information that is not critically important to your lesson."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two of the following are effective strategies to help students connect prior knowledge to new material?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask students what they know about a topic during an objective discussion.",
      "Include visuals, questions, or prompts in a warm-up"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a \"meaningful project\" according to Blumenfeld and Krajcik?",
    "answers": ["a student portfolio"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following best describes a \"sticky\" curriculum?",
    "answers": ["memorable, usable, durable"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which three of the following strategies are good examples of \"teacher talk?\"",
    "answers": [
      "Asking questions",
      "Using metaphors, analogies, or mnemonics",
      "Clarifying and elaborating"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of inductive reasoning?",
    "answers": ["Show students examples and have them figure out the rules."]
  },
  {
    "question": "A teacher reads a paragraph about an experience he or she has had, and then asks students to write a paragraph relating a similar experience of their own. This is an example of:",
    "answers": ["modeling"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two examples of guided instruction are:",
    "answers": [
      "Providing teacher-led activities to break down difficult tasks",
      "providing students with a Cloze exercise to help them apply new vocabulary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two of the following are examples of independent practice?",
    "answers": [
      "A homework assignment that applies a newly-learned concept",
      "A dialogue written and presented by student groups"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of memory learning? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": ["Multiplication tables", "Irregular verbs in English", "idioms"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two of the following objectives represent knowledge learning?",
    "answers": [
      "Students will create a poster illustrating the article.",
      "Students will write a letter to the editor voicing their opinion on the local elections"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these are reasons discussed in this module for why a “scarecrow” learner might struggle with reading? (Select all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Learners may lack “world knowledge” or the ability to apply what they’ve learned in other contexts to aid their understanding while reading.",
      "Learners may not know how to decode the letters and sounds that make up words.",
      "Learners may lack strategies for reading effectively.",
      "Learners may not know the “rules of the game” or conventions of different genres.",
      "Learners may not know vocabulary and understanding of simple sentence structure."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of learner does the Tin Man represent?",
    "answers": [
      "One who thinks reading is “passive,” so he or she does not connect reading with active strategies (like asking questions, predicting, thinking about the text, and evaluating the author’s ideas) and the need to interact with a text."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kind of learner does the Lion represent?",
    "answers": [
      "One who does not have enough background knowledge to make good predictions while reading, and so often cannot fully comprehend a text."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is tennis a good metaphor for reading?",
    "answers": [
      "Because reading is an active exchange between two players: the reader and the author."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Important skills for effective reading include... (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "The ability to make predictions.",
      "The ability to focus on meaning instead of sound.",
      "The ability to connect what one is reading to past knowledge or experience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Active reading will generally involve…",
    "answers": ["Pre-reading, reading, and post-reading activities"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Post-reading activities are a chance for… (check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Teachers to assess what students were able to comprehend and recall.",
      "Learners to apply, synthesize, and evaluate a reading."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Allowing students to find reading material that is of “high interest” to them as individuals is an example of…",
    "answers": ["Autonomy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these activities may be used as a pre-reading activity to build interest and connection to the text? (check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Having students scan the title and subheadings of the reading and make predictions about what they are about to read.",
      "Discussing a series of pictures related to the reading to see what students already know about the topic."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "How was Dorothy able to get the Lion to read? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "By making him want to read.",
      "By finding ways to intrigue him.",
      "By piquing his curiosity."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The goal of Coach Hare's reading method can be summarized by which 2 words:",
    "answers": ["Pleasure and Exposure"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Areas that are specifically designed to help promote reading among students are called:",
    "answers": ["Reading Zones"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A fill in the blank exercise can also be called a(n):",
    "answers": ["Cloze Passage."]
  },
  {
    "question": "How can a teacher assess extensive reading (mark all that apply)?",
    "answers": [
      "Character Maps",
      "Reading Reports",
      "Discussions",
      "Reading Logs",
      "Outlines",
      "Debates"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Some extensive reading critics argue that this reading approach is \"lazy\" because",
    "answers": ["Students are given a lot of free time to read."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which reading method is considered to be more teacher-centered?",
    "answers": ["Both Coach Hare's AND Coach Tortoise's methods"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which reading strategy can attempt to break down sentences into parts of speech, which can help learners understand the differences between verbs, nouns, adjectives, and adverbs.",
    "answers": ["Intensive Reading"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Coach Tortoise believes that:",
    "answers": ["Proficiency fuels passion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Newspaper corners, reading zones, jigsaws, morphology, and reading logs are all reading strategies that can be employed by an ESL teacher to improve reading fluency.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is the best reading strategy for middle school students?",
    "answers": ["A combination of both"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why might some students be overwhelmed by a writing assignment? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Unwillingness to seek help or feedback in the writing process.",
      "A lack of confidence about one’s ideas.",
      "Difficulty in coming up with ideas to write about.",
      "Fear of not meeting the teacher’s expectations."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The concept that writing is a process, not a product, means that:",
    "answers": [
      "Writing is a complex activity that should be broken up into different steps so that students don’t become confused and overwhelmed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In regards to writing activities, what does it mean to “prime the pump”?",
    "answers": [
      "Helping learners connect concepts and information they already know to new information and skills they will need in their writing."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is okay to grade students on things you did not write down in your instructions. All teachers have the same expectations, and students should already know those expectations before they get to your class!",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "You should never ask students to share their writing with their classmates because they will feel stupid or ridiculous.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Writing is like composing music in that…",
    "answers": [
      "It is important for both writers and composers (and painters and other artists!) to review their work, evaluate it, and make changes as needed."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "To “go global” while teaching writing means to focus on helping students develop organization, order, and ideas, as opposed to just grammar.",
    "answers": ["True."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Students should never challenge the teacher because the teacher is always right.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "“Appropriation” in writing is when students don’t like their teacher’s ideas and so write about a topic that is not appropriate to the assignment.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "A writing teacher should act mostly as a ________________.",
    "answers": ["Consultant."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon covered 3 best strategies that can help your students in the pre-writing stage. Which one is not mentioned?",
    "answers": ["Good writing is good listening."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Brainstorming should not be a group activity because students need to learn to develop their own ideas to write effectively.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In this module, Dr. Dixon taught us about the 6 Traits of Writing and how they can assist our students in the writing process. The 6 Traits of Writing are Ideas, Organization, Voice, Conventions, Word Choice, and:",
    "answers": ["Sentence Fluency"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Regardless of which strategy you employ in your writing class, it is important that you use modeling, guided practice, and _______________ in your lesson.",
    "answers": ["Independent Practice"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Correct punctuation, spelling, and formatting would all fall under which trait?",
    "answers": ["Conventions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "If the author neglects the audience-author connection, the reader may find that the story may be:",
    "answers": ["Boring"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the 6 Traits of Writing considers the audience-author connection?",
    "answers": ["Voice"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Using an outline is a good way to _____________ your writing.",
    "answers": ["build organization in"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Outlines, mind-webs, and ________ are three activites that our students can use to help them organize their ideas.",
    "answers": ["Paragraph Blocks"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When we have our students create outlines, we should check them over to make sure that there is correct grammar and voice; otherwise, they may have trouble in the “writing” stage of the process.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The theory of input enhancement was proposed by...",
    "answers": ["Mike Sharwood Smith"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is NOT a big question that was mentioned about teaching grammar?",
    "answers": ["Why is grammar so easy to teach?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these is NOT an example of enhancing input?",
    "answers": ["Putting the princess on a bunch of mattresses."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the noticing hypothesis?",
    "answers": [
      "That learners cannot learn the grammatical features of a language unless they FIRST notice them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are important to remember when teaching grammar? Choose 2.",
    "answers": [
      "That learners are on their own subconscious schedule -- not your curriculum calendar.",
      "That teachers need to create multiple opportunities for learners to see forms that might be tricky for them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Some reading and writing assignments may create demand for certain kinds of grammatical forms. This can present an opportunity for you, as the teacher, to briefly stop and have a grammar noticing activity.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Research by Merrill Swain suggested which of the following?",
    "answers": [
      "Even when students are immersed in language, they don't just \"pick up\" all of the grammar forms."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "We suggest that one of the teacher's jobs when teaching grammar is to...",
    "answers": [
      "Help students pay attention to things they are not noticing, such as grammar forms or grammar errors."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are ways to help students notice grammar in your reading/writing lessons? Choose all that are correct.",
    "answers": [
      "Creating lessons that encourage learners to use specific grammatical items.",
      "Repeating something in class.",
      "Using bolded phrases, italics, or underlining."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When incorporating grammar into a reading/writing class, teachers should remember that the ultimate goal is...",
    "answers": [
      "To help learners communicate their message and achieve their goals."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three kinds of non-readers discussed in Module 1? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "The \"Scarecrow Reader,\" who does not have enough background knowledge to make good predictions while reading, and so often cannot fully comprehend a text.",
      "The \"Tin Man Reader,\" one who thinks reading is “passive,” so he or she does not connect reading with active strategies (like asking questions, predicting, thinking about the text, and evaluating the author’s ideas) and the need to interact with a text.",
      "The \"Lion Reader,\" one who thinks that reading is a waste of time and so does not enjoy it, preferring instead to watch movies or interact on social media."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Module 1, what is Dorothy's advice to non-readers?",
    "answers": [
      "Ask questions while reading.",
      "Before and as you read, predict what will happen in the text.",
      "Think critically while reading."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the expression “writing is best viewed as a process rather than a product?” mean in the context of this course?",
    "answers": [
      "Writing is a complex activity that can be aided by careful writing activities."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some ways a teacher might let students know what she or he expects from a writing assignment? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Give them specifics on the length of the paper, due dates, and basic writing conventions (font size, margin size, etc.)",
      "Provide a model (example) for students.",
      "Give them specific vocabulary you are looking for."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one of the most important things you can do after students write?",
    "answers": [
      "Have students discuss their writing with each other (peer review)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Some students feel overwhelmed at the thought of writing because",
    "answers": ["All of the above."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is recursive writing?",
    "answers": ["Reviewing your writing, evaluating, and making changes."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does it mean to “go global” with writing?",
    "answers": [
      "To make changes in organization, order, and in the ideas themselves."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why should we, as teachers, avoid “appropriation?”",
    "answers": [
      "Because we value our students’ ideas and language, and want to see how they express themselves in writing."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Grammar is the most important part of a writing class. Students should have perfect grammar before they begin to develop text organization, paragraph structure, and coherent ideas.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reading activities should be very teacher-centered.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which reading strategy can attempt to break down sentences into parts of speech, which can help learners understand the differences between verbs, nouns, adjectives, and adverbs?",
    "answers": ["Intensive Reading"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The 6 Traits of Writing are Ideas, Organization, _____________, Sentence Fluency, _________________________, and Word Choice.",
    "answers": ["Conventions.", "Voice."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why might a writer wish to use an outline in his writing process?",
    "answers": ["To build organization."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Every step of the writing process should be individual so that each writer can produce a unique assignment.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon covered 3 best strategies for that can help your students in the pre-writing stage. Which one was not mentioned?",
    "answers": ["Good writing is good speaking."]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Noticing\" is important when it comes to teaching and learning grammatical writing.",
    "answers": ["True."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Reading and writing teachers should only pay attention to individual learner problems when it comes to grammar.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is some grammar instruction important?",
    "answers": [
      "Language learners are not likely to use grammar accurately unless we give grammar some special attention."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Grammar points can be introduced at random. It doesn't really matter what grammar a teacher is teaching, as long as she/he is remembering to teach grammar.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the review video, Dr. Dixon mentioned that he hopes that the lessons discussed in this course are \"sticky.\" What does it mean for a lesson to be \"sticky\"?",
    "answers": ["Easy to remember and bring to mind in related situations."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon's example of his 2-year old's speech, \"Daddy! Read? Snuggle? Where's blankie?\" is an example of",
    "answers": ["a pragmatic reduction."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following are examples of paralinguistic variables? (Select all correct answers.)",
    "answers": ["Volume", "An accent", "Speed of speech", "Gestures"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which words below refer to informal speech that is not often used in writing and can often contain difficult to understand idiomatic expressions that must be taught one by one?",
    "answers": ["Fillers", "Slang", "Colloquialisms"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The vocabulary in all of the English-speaking countries is always exactly the same.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Select the examples of performance variables below:",
    "answers": ["\"Wait....\"", "\"Well....\"", "\"Um.....\""]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the challenges listening and speaking teachers face in the classroom? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Teachers can be tricked into believing that class time is an opportunity for students to listen, and for a teacher to speak.",
      "It is difficult to let everyone's voice be heard, and it is easier for teachers to listen to the voices they prefer or listen to those teachers believe are smarter than others.",
      "A teacher's focus on short term goals such as memorizing facts can become an impediment to language learning itself."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some forms of oral discourse discussed in this module? (Select all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Monologues",
      "Transactional Dialogues",
      "Interactional Dialogues"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which feature of spoken language is used to increase the speed of conversation by simply leaving out already understood information?",
    "answers": ["Pragmatic Reductions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: It is easy to get students to share and collaborate in another language.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Listening is challenging for both students and teachers, but for different reasons.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Listening strategies\" is a concept that is easy to define.",
    "answers": [
      "False.  Though definitions for \"listening strategies\" vary among researchers, we defined listening strategies as any techniques that learners use to overcome the difficulty of listening, including requests for elaboration, requests for clarification, and note-taking (among others)."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Learners should always avoid risk when choosing a listening strategy.",
    "answers": [
      "False.  All strategies involve some level of risk, but no one ever learned a language without taking some risks!"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Recording a lecture in order to listen to it later (and thus avoid missing key information) is what kind of listening strategy?",
    "answers": ["Attempt to slow things down to learn at one's own pace."]
  },
  {
    "question": "One strategy discussed involves connecting listening to reading and writing so that information is coming in through two channels - the audio channel and the visual channel. How do we propose learners connect listening to reading and writing?",
    "answers": [
      "Through effective note-taking, such as the Cornell Method of Note-taking."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Very general, open-ended questions and tasks are best for teaching listening skills.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are three activities teachers can invite students to do before, during, or after listening to an audio?",
    "answers": [
      "Listen for specific details.",
      "Discuss or free-write about what they already know about the topic, then relax and listen for main ideas.",
      "Take notes and then summarize the audio."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Discussing or free-writing about what they already know about a topic, then relaxing and listening for main ideas is an example of _____________________.",
    "answers": ["Top-down processing."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Focusing learners' attentions on specific questions or details while listening is an example of ______________________________.",
    "answers": ["Bottom-up processing."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is there any one strategy that EVERYONE (all teachers, researchers, and students) agree is the best strategy to develop listening skills?",
    "answers": [
      "No, but there is a wide consensus of some ways to effectively approach teaching listening in the ESL context."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ultimately, a listening teacher's job is to ___________________",
    "answers": [
      "Provide a variety of paths, techniques, and strategies for students to approach listening."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the 5-hour problem?",
    "answers": [
      "That the standard amount of time dedicated to language learning in most programs doesn't give students enough exposure to language."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which 3 of the following are related to how easily a speaker's emotions can be influenced by others?",
    "answers": ["Interlocutor effect", "Interaction effect"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When students listen carefully and repeat exactly what a speaker says, what kind of speaking is this?",
    "answers": ["Imitative speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a teacher listens to a student for the purpose of finding out how accurately the student can speak, what kind of speaking is this?",
    "answers": ["Intensive speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Your student will have to take the TOEFL next week. What kind of speaking will he/she engage in during the timed prompt?",
    "answers": ["Responsive speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are going to meet a student for a conference about his grades. What kind of speaking will you two engage in?",
    "answers": ["Interactive speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why does the Teach English Now! team prefer Adam and Ashley's style of teaching to Clara Fication's style of teaching? Choose 3 answers.",
    "answers": [
      "Because it motivates learners",
      "Because it stimulates critical thinking about the material",
      "Because it evokes a warm, inviting classroom atmosphere"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the illusion of interactivity?",
    "answers": [
      "When students seem to be speaking the target language a lot in class, but really they aren't."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When thinking back on different language approaches throughout the years, what kinds of speaking were most common in TESOL classrooms? Choose 2.",
    "answers": ["Intensive speaking", "Imitative speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Adam says that imitative and intensive speaking activities have a place in the modern language classroom. What is his reasoning? Choose 2 answers.",
    "answers": [
      "Because imitative and intensive speaking can give students, especially basic-level students, a valuable opportunity for practice.",
      "As discussed in the first specialization, we don't want to swing too far to one side of the pendulum."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Good language learners have a tendency to prepare and practice more than other language learners.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Even if learners approach a task differently, they can use the same general strategies regardless of their personalities or personal learning style preferences.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some techniques associated with the concept of imagery? Choose the 4 correct answers.",
    "answers": ["mnemonic devices", "images", "mind palaces", "pictures"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is interactivity?",
    "answers": ["speaking with others"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is interactivity one of the keys to improving speaking skills? Choose the 3 best answers.",
    "answers": [
      "Because it helps students to focus on the task.",
      "Because it involves risk-taking.",
      "Because critical feedback can be given."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "It is not necessary for teachers to help students express their new identities.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What kinds of questions will help students to speak up in class? Choose the 3 correct answers.",
    "answers": [
      "questions that require critical thinking",
      "questions about students likes and dislikes",
      "questions that allow students to express their thoughts"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is it important to give students tasks that allow them to use authentic language? Choose the 2 correct answers.",
    "answers": [
      "Because it is motivating to students.",
      "Because it will better engage students in the tasks."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which classroom is the ideal classroom to help motivate students to speak?",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Shane, impossible tasks are truly impossible and should be avoided in the classroom.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the field of education, what does the concept of \"recycling\" refer to?",
    "answers": ["discussing information that was previously covered"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Elements that are considered OUTSIDE of normal linguistic elements are known as...",
    "answers": ["paralinguistic elements"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Many language learners don't want to give up their accent because their accents are representative of their identities. What linguistic concept is this?",
    "answers": ["language ego"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon stated that pronunciation is multifaceted -- there are a lot of factors that affect it! Which of the following factors might influence learners' pronunciation in a new language? Choose all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "1st language",
      "regionalisms",
      "language ego",
      "age",
      "stress",
      "intonation",
      "prestige accents",
      "innate phonetic ability",
      "reductions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Two types of reductions are (1) assimilations and (2) lexical elisions. What does each term mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Assimilations are when sounds change and blend together. Lexical elisions are when speakers drop sounds in the middle or at the end of words."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When learners start noticing and correcting their own mistakes, what is this referred to as?",
    "answers": ["monitoring"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ways to practice pronunciation include... (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "articulation activities",
      "analyzing examples of reduced speech forms",
      "discussing written v. spoken language",
      "tongue twisters",
      "dialogues"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between a global and a local error?",
    "answers": [
      "A global error is when a speaker makes the error in an international setting, and a local error is when the speaker makes an error in his home setting."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is spot correction?",
    "answers": [
      "When a teacher corrects a student at the time the error is made"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "You are working on pronunciation with your students. First, you choose a sound which many students are struggling with. Then, you have students listen to sentences with minimal pairs containing that sound. Finally, you have students use tongue twisters with that sound. What strategy did you just use?",
    "answers": ["compare, identify, produce"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a phrase is left out in between two thoughts and the listener is asked to add in the missing details by predicting or relying on the context, this is called",
    "answers": ["Ellipses"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some features that teachers--especially new teachers--use that can make listening hard for learners? (Check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Speaking too low.",
      "Using idioms, regionalisms and slang.",
      "Speaking too fast.",
      "Speaking too slow."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fillers and redundancies are examples of performance variables.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the examples below demonstrates the concept of \"blending?\"",
    "answers": ["Idonwanna."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which options are strategies learners can use to improve their own listening skills? Select all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Wait until another, more appropriate time to seek clarification",
      "Request for elaboration",
      "Request for clarification"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term used for when learners start noticing and correcting their own mistakes?",
    "answers": ["Monitoring"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which note taking style was discussed in which learners took notes about details of a lecture in class, reviewed notes after class and wrote key points, and finally wrote a summary of the notes?",
    "answers": ["The Cornell Method"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Teachers should view listening activities as a time where the teacher simply starts an audio recording, sit down, and let students alone.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which listening process requires listeners to focus on details or a specific part of a listening passage?",
    "answers": ["Bottom up process"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How are classroom size and the 5-hour problem related?",
    "answers": [
      "They both have a positive influence on how students feel and behave."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When students are required to produce short segments of language that demonstrate grammatical, lexical and/or phonologice accuracy, what kind of speaking is this?",
    "answers": ["Intensive speaking"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are positive or negative emotions which influence a person's ability to speak?",
    "answers": ["Affective Factors"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: It is never appropriate to use intensive and imitative speaking activities in the classroom.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the purpose of mentioning the phrase, \"You can't tell the storm under the surface\" in relation to teaching language learners? Select all that apply",
    "answers": [
      "When students speak, they have a lot going in on their minds, such as focusing on their grammar and pronunciation, in addition to the ideas they're sharing.",
      "As teachers, we often do not know what's going on in our students' minds.",
      "Teachers should take into consideration that social cues demand pleasantness so speakers are required to appear calm and happy, even when inside, they are managing all kinds of pressure."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which students typically speak more in language courses?",
    "answers": [
      "Students who focus on how they they say things:  the \"focus-on-form\" students."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which speaking strategies were discussed in Module 4?",
    "answers": ["Physical Response", "Practice", "Preparation", "Imagery"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How do sociolinguists define the silent period?",
    "answers": ["a stage in which learners are unable or unwilling to speak"]
  },
  {
    "question": "True or False: Teachers should NEVER elicit imitative, intensive or responsive speech in their classrooms.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some techniques associated with the concept of imagery? Choose the correct answers.",
    "answers": ["Mind palaces", "Mnemonic devices", "Images", "Pictures"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the variables that make second language pronunciation difficult, thereby producing significant accents?",
    "answers": [
      "Reductions",
      "Paralinguistics",
      "First language",
      "Innate phonetic ability",
      "Age"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these questions should teachers consider when deciding how to teach pronunciation? Check all that apply.",
    "answers": [
      "Is our goal as language teachers to remove accent from the first language entirely or to improve intelligibility?",
      "What factors might affect my students' pronunciation in English?",
      "Are pronunciation and identity connected?",
      "Should a certain accent be taught in the classroom?"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to the information in Module 5, which accent would be a \"prestige accent\" in the United States.",
    "answers": ["An Irish Accent"]
  },
  {
    "question": "An error that causes interference with meaning is known as a",
    "answers": ["Global Error"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some techniques teachers can use to make listening easier for students?",
    "answers": [
      "Pause listening passages periodically to discuss and simplify meaning.",
      "Encourage students to ask their own questions.",
      "Ask students comprehension questions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In this module, Dr. Dixon mentions several reasons why teachers don’t use technology. Check 3 of those reasons below.",
    "answers": [
      "Teachers might feel overwhelmed by the amount of new technology constantly being thrown at them.",
      "Technology can be seen as a waste of time and money.",
      "Technology might be unavailable or limited in some schools or regions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two pieces of advice does Dr. Dixon give for those in technology-scarce areas?",
    "answers": [
      "Learn as much as you can about the tools that could help your school and share them with others.",
      "Find out what resources exist in your school and use them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "To save time, choose technologies for the classroom as quickly as possible.",
    "answers": ["False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Dr. Dixon, why do some teachers view technology as a waste of time? (Please check the three that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Technological tools can take a long time to learn how to use and manage.",
      "It can take the teacher a long time to understand the technology.",
      "Sometimes technology won’t turn on or won’t load during a lesson."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Curriculum and technology must be aligned. What does this mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Know what your objectives are and then choose a technology that fits those objectives."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Control technology or it will control you. What does this mean in relation to teaching?",
    "answers": [
      "Create clear guidelines for your learners so that the learners don’t create their own guidelines."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When choosing technology, you should consider your objectives and outcomes first and then examine how the technology and textbooks could fit in.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Balance happens when you are outcomes driven. What does this mean? (Check the 3 that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Find technology to support what you teach after you have decided on or reviewed your objectives.",
      "Look at your tests, look at your objectives and outcomes, and see how you can incorporate technology to reach those outcomes.",
      "First, you should have a strong idea of what you want learners to achieve."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "One of the biggest mistakes that inexperienced teachers make is that they incorporate new technologies without thinking about how it fits in with their current curricular design.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What was the result of Dr. Dixon’s research on two groups of learners using an online pronunciation website?",
    "answers": [
      "The learners who followed a carefully prepared curriculum that was aligned with the objectives of the course were more motivated."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "1. Dr. Dixon gave a few examples of LMS options for teachers. Which of the following did he mention? ain.",
    "answers": [
      "Blackboard",
      "Edmodo",
      "Schoology",
      "Moodle",
      "Google Classroom"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following could be used to interact with students digitally? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": ["Facebook", "Twitter", "Email", "Blogs", "Vlogs", "Skype"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following Microsoft Office programs would be considered as a word processing application?",
    "answers": ["Word"]
  },
  {
    "question": "According to Dr. Dixon, which category would house Learning Management Systems?",
    "answers": ["Category #4: Communication and Collaboration"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the disadvantages of using an LMS? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Students have a very difficult time adapting to lessons that use technology.",
      "Not all of them are free.",
      "Teachers will have to invest time into learning how to use it.-"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Category 5: Instructional Media includes which of the following examples: (Check the 3 answers that apply.)",
    "answers": ["TedX", "Discovery Education Streaming", "Khan Academy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following does not belong in the 6 events of instruction:",
    "answers": ["Event 5: Implement Technology"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Google Docs and Microsoft Word have a feature that allows the teacher to “Track Changes”. This is a highly useful technological tool that could be used to enhance which of the 6 events?",
    "answers": [
      "Event 6: Assessment and Feedback",
      "Event #6: Assessment and Feedback"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A teacher can use a variety of applications that span all of the technology categories to enhance student learning for each of the 6 events of instruction.",
    "answers": ["True"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Whether you are comfortable using technology in the classroom, or not, you should always remember that:",
    "answers": [
      "The teacher should control the use technology in the classroom.",
      "The teacher should control the use of technology in the classroom."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the TPACK model examine?",
    "answers": [
      "The combination of content, pedagogical, and technological knowledge."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the SAMR model examine?",
    "answers": [
      "The combination of substitution, augmentation, modification and redefinition in relation to teaching with technology.",
      "How integrating technology changes a learning task to improve the learning experience."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "If we compare the stages of SAMR to rungs on a ladder, how are the stages positioned?",
    "answers": [
      "Substitution and augmentation are at the bottom, while modification and redefinition are at the top",
      "Substitution and augmentation are at the bottom, while modification and redefinition are at the top."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Replacing a traditional learning task or resource with a technology-based one is an example of...",
    "answers": ["substitution"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Asking students to review a list of media resources, evaluate the information, and then develop their own video presentation is an example of...",
    "answers": ["redefinition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a teacher integrates video resources into an online textbook, this is an example of...",
    "answers": ["augmentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Giving students a list of media resources, asking them to decide which information is important, and letting them construct their own knowledge is an example of...",
    "answers": ["modification"]
  },
  {
    "question": "TPACK combines several types of knowledge to produce several new types of knowledge. One of these new types of knowledge is Pedagogical Content Knowledge. What is Pedagogical Content Knowledge?",
    "answers": ["knowing what to teach and how to teach it"]
  },
  {
    "question": "TPACK combines several types of knowledge to produce several new types of knowledge. One of these new types of knowledge is Technological Content Knowledge. What is Technological Content Knowledge?",
    "answers": [
      "knowing what to teach and how technology can be used to teach it"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "TPACK combines several types of knowledge to produce several new types of knowledge. One of these new types of knowledge is Technological Pedagogical Knowledge. What is Technological Pedagogical Knowledge?",
    "answers": [
      "what teachers know about technology and about teaching in order to apply technology to different teaching situations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When you're trying to navigate through the vast sea of educational technology products, remember to... (Check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Keep your objectives in mind",
      "Remain curious",
      "Consult other technology users",
      "Use the SAMR model"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "This course is self-paced so that you can complete it at your own speed. Which one of Richard Mayer's principles does this illustrate?",
    "answers": ["the interactive principle", "The Interactive Principle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Course 4, before we talked about how to work with different kinds of readers, we had Dorothy and a cast of colorful characters act out common situations in a reading/writing classroom. Which one of Richard Mayer's principles does this illustrate?",
    "answers": ["the pre-training principle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Instead of doing \"talking head\" videos, our videos contained a lot of fun and \"sticky\" pictures and images. Which of Richard Mayer's principles does this illustrate?",
    "answers": ["the multimedia principle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Jessica and Shane's videos were crafted to be inviting conversations with you, the learner. Which of Richard Mayer's principles does this illustrate?",
    "answers": [
      "the personalization principle",
      "The Personalization Principle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Shane's friend who was a discus thrower created an iBook so that she could use words and videos to communicate her message. This is an example of using which model effectively?",
    "answers": ["SAMR"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does \"Tri\" represent?",
    "answers": [
      "redefining technology to transform students' learning experiences"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Richard Mayer's principles are only useful for online teaching. They have no relevance to the brick and mortar classroom.",
    "answers": ["False."]
  },
  {
    "question": "In his successful Technology Final Exam, Newbie tells the vendors that he needs a technology that will help his students create presentations. What is this an example of?",
    "answers": [
      "Keeping your objectives in mind when searching for new technology"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Why is remembering the SAMR model so important when evaluating and purchasing new technology?",
    "answers": [
      "because it helps you evaluate whether the technology in question is integral and important to the lesson or activity you're creating",
      "It helps you evaluate whether the technology in question is integral and important to the lesson or activity you're creating"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "In the first module, Dr. Dixon mentioned several reasons why teachers don’t use technology. Check 3 of those reasons below.",
    "answers": [
      "Teachers might feel overwhelmed by the amount of new technology constantly being thrown at them.",
      "Technology can be seen as a waste of time and money.",
      "Technology might be unavailable or limited in some schools or regions."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which two pieces of advice does Dr. Dixon give for those in technology-scarce areas? (Check two answers.)",
    "answers": [
      "Learn as much as you can about the tools that could help your school and share them with others.",
      "Find out what resources exist in your school and use them."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Curriculum and technology must be aligned. What does that mean?",
    "answers": [
      "Know what your objectives are and then choose a technology that fits those objectives."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some of the disadvantages of using an LMS? (Check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "Teachers will have to invest time into learning how to use it.",
      "Not all of your students may have continuous access to technology/internet.",
      "Not all of them are free."
    ]
  },

  {
    "question": "What does the acronym “COIK” stand for?",
    "answers": ["Clear Only If Known"]
  },
  {
    "question": "12. As an educator, how do we try to avoid COIK?",
    "answers": [
      "Move slowly with your students and assume that they do not know everything that you will teach during your lesson."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some indicators of technophobia? (Check all that apply)",
    "answers": [
      "The learner is afraid that the technology may malfunction.",
      "The learner is afraid of exploring a technology.",
      "The learner is afraid that the technology won’t do what they want it to.",
      "The learner is afraid that they may break the technology."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is “Just in Time Advice”?",
    "answers": [
      "The teacher should number or categorize the task for the student."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following learners will need your support?",
    "answers": ["All of the above"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does the SAMR model examine? (Choose two answers)",
    "answers": [
      "How integrating technology changes a learning task to improve the learning experience",
      "The combination of substitution, augmentation, modification and redefinition in relation to teaching with technology."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When a teacher integrates video resources into an online textbook, which stage of SAMR is this an example of?",
    "answers": ["Augmentation"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Giving students a list of media resources, asking them to decide which information is important, and letting them construct their own knowledge is an example of which SAMR stage?",
    "answers": ["Redefinition"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In Course 4, before discussing how to work with different kinds of readers, Dorothy and a cast of colorful characters acted out common situations in a reading/writing classroom. Which one of Richard Mayer's principles does this illustrate?",
    "answers": ["The Pre-Training Principle"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are some indicators of technophobia? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "The learner is afraid of exploring a technology.",
      "The learner is afraid that the technology won't do what they want it to.",
      "The learner is afraid the technology may malfunction.",
      "The learner is afraid that they may break the technology."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following examples best describes a digital native?",
    "answers": ["A person who has an intuitive feel for different devices"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Of the following types of learners, which ones would be considered digital natives? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": ["Learner #2", "Learner #3"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon provided three suggestions on how to support Learner #1. (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Provide more guided activities",
      "Give non-natives tutorials",
      "Pair students according to skill level"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "As an educator, how do we try to avoid COIK (Clear Only If Known)?",
    "answers": [
      "Move slowly with your students and assume that they do not know everything you will teach during your lesson."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon provided two suggestions on how to support Learner #2. What were they? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": ["Set clear boundaries", "Limit the distractions"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is one way a teacher could set boundaries for their students?",
    "answers": ["Pomodoro Technique"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dr. Dixon provided two suggestions on how to support Learner #3. What were they? (Check all that apply.)",
    "answers": [
      "Set clear boundaries",
      "Make sure they are following the directions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is \"Just in Time\" advice?",
    "answers": ["Letting students choose how they want to approach the task"]
  }
]


